questions = [{

	'question' : ' Which law of newton states about inertia and state of condition in physics? ',
	'options'  : [1,2,3,4],
	'correct_ans' : 2
},
{

	'question' : 'Which city in india is know as pink city?',
	'options'  : ['dehradun','jaipur','raipur','mohali'],
	'correct_ans' : 'jaipur'
},
{

	'question' : 'The Kishkindha is located in which state of india?',
	'options'  : ['tamil nadu', 'odisha', 'Karnataka', 'kerala'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Karnataka'
},
{

	'question' : 'What is the national flower of India?',
	'options'  : ['Lotus','Rhododendron','Golden Shower','Not declared'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Lotus'
},
{

	'question' : 'Which of the following states is not located in the North?',
	'options'  : ['Jharkhand', 'Jammu and Kashmir', 'Himachal Pradesh', 'Haryana'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Jharkhand'
},
{

	'question' : 'In which of the following state, the main language is Khasi?',
	'options'  : ['Mizoram', 'Nagaland', 'Meghalaya', 'Tripura'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Meghalaya'
},
{

	'question' : 'Which is the largest gold reserve of india?',
	'options'  : ['Kerala', 'hampi', 'kolar', 'Arunachal Pradesh'],
	'correct_ans' : 'kolar'
},
{

	'question' : ' Which state has the largest area?',
	'options'  : ['Maharashtra', 'Madhya Pradesh', 'Uttar Pradesh', 'Rajasthan'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Rajasthan'
},
{

	'question' : 'Which state has the largest population?',
	'options'  : ['Uttar Pradesh', 'Maharastra', 'Bihar', 'Andra Pradesh'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Uttar Pradesh'
},
{

	'question' : ' In what state is Elephant Falls located?',
	'options'  : ['Mizoram', 'Orissa', 'Manipur', 'Meghalaya'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Meghalaya'
},
{

	'question' : ' Which of the following device converts chemical energy in to electrical energy?',
	'options'  : ['Battery', 'Loud Speaker', 'Solar Cell', 'Electric Motor'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Battery'
},
{

	'question' : 'The energy possessed by a body due to its position is called:',
	'options'  : ['Kinetic Energy', 'Potential Energy', 'Mechanical Energy', 'Electrical Energy'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Potential Energy'
},
{

	'question' : 'Joule is a unit of:',
	'options'  : ['Work', 'Power', 'Momentum', 'None of the above'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Work'
},
{

	'question' : ' The commercial unit of Energy is:',
	'options'  : ['Watt', 'Watt-hour', 'Kilowatt-hour', 'Kilowatt'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Kilowatt-hour'
},
{

	'question' : 'When an object falls freely towards the ground, then its total energy:',
	'options'  : ['Increases', 'Decreases', 'Remains constant', 'First increases then decreases'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Remains constant'
},
{

	'question' : 'In 1 minute how much energy does a 100 W electric bulb transfers?',
	'options'  : ['100 J', '600 J', '3600 J', '6000 J'],
	'correct_ans' : '6000 J'
},
{

	'question' : 'What happens to the body on which work is done:',
	'options'  : ['It loses energy', 'It gains energy', 'No change in the energy', 'First it loses then it gain'],
	'correct_ans' : 'It gains energy'
},
{

	'question' : 'A radio set of 60 watts runs for 50 hours. How many units of electrical energy are consumed in kWh?',
	'options'  : ['2 kWh', '3 kWh', '4 kWh', '2.5 kWh'],
	'correct_ans' : '3 kWh'
},
{

	'question' : 'What is the smallest unit of power?',
	'options'  : ['Watt', 'Kilowatt', 'Horse power', 'Milliwatt'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Watt'
},
{

	'question' : 'On an object the work done does not depend upon:',
	'options'  : ['Displacement', 'Angle between force and displacement', 'Force applied', 'Initial velocity of an object'],
	'correct_ans' : 'Initial velocity of an object'
}
]